Philip Vasilchenko iOS Developer

site: https://artfeel.github.io e-mail: philip.vasilchenko@gmail.com github: https://github.com/ArtFeel mobile: +38 (093) 903-96-40 skype: www.artfeel

Personal Profile

I'm results-oriented software developer with more than five years of experience. Mostly on the iOS platform (10 completed projects), passed evolution from iOS 4 up to iOS 10 version. But also I have an experience on the cross-platform mobile game development with Unity (C#). Experienced in AppStore submission process, App analytics and business development.

Work Experience

Cosmos & Paradox Kyiv, Ukraine.

Oct 2015 - Present

Game Development: We are working on an indie game called Yum Yum Sam. In process we use Unity, C# and Spine to create awesome animations and experience.

Mobile Applications: We offer native iOS application development services: everything necessary to produce a fully-fledged, stable mobile app solution.

MEGOGO.NET Kyiv, Ukraine.

May 2013 — Jan 2016

Megogo.net: Official iOS application for a Megogo.net digital media portal. Application includes all features available on the site, in-app purchases, subscriptions system, advertising inside video, custom video player with support of HTTP Live Streaming and Widevine DRM.

JETME Kyiv, Ukraine.

Jan 2014 — Mar 2014

JetMe: iPhone application for JETME Inc. JetMe allows you to search, book and pay for the private jet right in the app. With JetMe you can share the Private Jet with your friend!

Stanfy Kyiv, Ukraine.

Sep 2012 - May 2013

Signature App: iPad app for internal use by companies that organize conferences and events. Allows customers to gather information and signatures of participants. Can work offline and synchronize with the server on demand.

SongHi Audio Sequencer: iOS audio engine for a music sequencer, which would reproduce melodies played on various musical instruments, together with special audio effects.

eCommerce App: Universal Marketplace App for iPhone and iPad. Apps provide easy access to one of the biggest European supermarkets on iOS and Android mobile devices to create shopping lists, buy and order groceries delivery.

MLSDev Donetsk, Ukraine.

May 2011 — Jul 2012

Rocket Space: Rocket Space is a mobile arcade game, where one is to fly a rocket and avoid obstructions. Game is available on iOS, Android and Kindle Fire. Written in Lua (Corona SDK).

vTuner for Alpine: vTuner internet radio gives you access to thousands of radio stations from across the globe. Conveniently play your favorite stations using the Alpine car sound system.

iTaxi: Application that allows users to call a taxi quickly using their GPS location.

GPS Alarm: S-5000. New generation of car alarm system controlled by mobile phone. Written in C#/WPF for Windows desktop.

Key Skills

Objective-C Memory Management CocoaPods
KVC/KVO AVFoundation Unity 3D
UIKit CoreGraphics Swift
GCD StoreKit Cedar (UnitTesting)

Education

Computer Academy «Step»

Software Development

Donetsk, Ukraine, Grade: 5/5

Team leader of «CoreInvader» team, represented Ukraine at the final of Microsoft ImagineCup'10 at Poland.

Open International University of Human Development «Ukraine»

Finance and Credit, Bachelor

Mykolayiv, Ukraine, Grade: 5/5